<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Granada On</title>
    <link>https://granada-on.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Granada On</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://granada-on.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Granada On, the book</title>
      <link>https://granada-on.github.io/post/default/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://granada-on.github.io/post/default/</guid>
      <description>Granada On, the book This book is about Granada, a living city that exists before, during and after the Alhambra, the paella and the shopping. It is about the graffiti, about the technology, about urban exploration and about stuff that is in plain sight and yet almost never seen.
It is about a city to be lived and walked and eaten and drunk. A city that has to be discovered over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Granada On</title>
      <link>https://granada-on.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 08:50:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://granada-on.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>What this is about &amp;ldquo;Granada On&amp;rdquo; is, first and foremost, a book about one of the most awesome cities in the world, Granada in Spain. It is a book about a living and breathing city, a lived-in city. And it is also a living and evolving book, written by someone that has lived in Granada most of his life. Most guidebooks include a narrow concept of beauty or noteworthiness by selecting a few places based on some criteria that is difficult to ascertain, but which makes all places essentially the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy the book</title>
      <link>https://granada-on.github.io/post/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://granada-on.github.io/post/book/</guid>
      <description> Buy the book The book is for sale in all Amazon shops with a size that can be easily carried in your back pocket. And it&amp;rsquo;s cheaper than a dish of paella in one of the tourist traps in the city center, so it will save you money.
 Closer to home, in the UK
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy the eBook</title>
      <link>https://granada-on.github.io/post/ebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://granada-on.github.io/post/ebook/</guid>
      <description> Buy the book Buy the ebook for your mobile phone or simply to save money and help the planet. It&amp;rsquo;s DRM-free and also has a free license, so feel free and happy to share.
 Closer to home, in the UK
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>